Guide to the Susan Christopherson papers, circa 1983-2016.
Christopherson, Susan papers,
- Series IV. Correspondence
  - Communications G. LeRoy, etc., 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    Letters from Phil McMichael and Sam Cole, along with e-mail blasts from Greg LeRoy (Good Jobs First)
  - Cardiff Visit, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Ann Forsyth's An exam question for Susan Chistopherson (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence related to comments on her publications, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and notes, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Series V. Miscellaneous
  - Suburban Sprawl/Uneven Development Reading, Undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
    Readings and notes
  - Follow Up - Job Search Proposal, Undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
    A sheet of paper headed Job Search Proposal/ follow-up
  - Pierre-Andrew Memo, 1999-09-04 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    Memo from Pierre Clavel on obtaining employment and other economic statistics for NYS, as well as thinking though interview structure. Contains SMC notes
  - To-Do List, Undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
    A to-do list of work and home tasks
  - Recommendations Pending, 2014-05-27-2014-11-06 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    Requests for recommendations from former-Ph.D. students (for jobs, post-docs, and awards), plus a note from Alan Scott requesting SMC write a letter of support for an effort to have Michael Storper honored by the Association of American Geographers
    Access restrictions apply
  - Equity BK FRWARD, Undated (Box 19, Folder 52)
    Notes for a foreword to a book edited by Norman Krumholz, tentatively entitled Advancing Equity Planning that came out of a symposium that was held in honor of Krumholz's 90th birthday. The project was designed by Krumholz and Kathryn Hexter at Cleveland State University, in cooperation with SMC.
  - University Impact Articles, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    Contains materials related to the Cornell University Economic Impact on New York State report of Feb. 2007, including notes for a talk and early thoughts for a paper on role of universities in economic development. Also, related papers from other studies.
  - Susan's Notes, Date Unknown (Box 19, Folder 54)
    Sheets of handwritten notes with titles including: Notes from Convergences/Divergences Symposium (April 2001); Comments/Ideas from Economics literature on Location of Vertically Linked Industries; Ideas for Regions, Governence and the Global Economy CRP 800; Notes for Regional Comp Paper/Firm Strategies; Notes for Regional Comp Paper; Notes from Lovering
  - Bellagio Application, Date Unknown (Box 19, Folder 55)
    Notes on different ideas for a conference at Bellagio
  - Book Contract, 2004-05-24 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    Contract and related materials for SMC book with Jennifer Clark, Remaking Regional Economies
  - Economic Development: SMC; JC, 2004-2007; CD-3844-3847 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    Disks and marketing description, along with shipping receipt for Remaking Regional Economies
  - Contacts, 1992-2003 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    Note, includes a 1992 letter from Allen Pred
  - Contacts/Europe 1993, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Humberto, Undated (Box 19, Folder 60)
    A letter to a student regarding his work.
  - J. Martin, 2006-05 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    Comments on J. Martin Dissertation
  - Anouk, 2005-04 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    Comments on Anouk Patel-Campillo graduate work
  - Daniel Sandoval, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    Comments on dissertation and related notes
  - Speaking Invitation, 2004-12-02 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    Invitation from Neil Wrigley and Gordon Clark to speak at a Journal of Economic Geography sponsored session at the British Academy of Management meetings
  - Fordham University Press Contract, 2011 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    Contract from Fordham University Press for a book on media, and comments from a former editor on the contract
  - NYSARC, 2004-08-23 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    An e-mail from David Brown regarding SMC being in contact with the New York State Association of Regional Councils
  - Policy Ideas, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Business Cards, Undated (Box 21)
  - Ned's slides for urban planning course: The european city, 1995-07 (Box 22)
    Slide boxes
  - Siena and Florence, 1995-07 (Box 22)
  - San Francisco, Library, Yerba Buena Gardens, 1996-08 (Box 22)
  - Boston, San Francisco, 1996-09 (Box 22)
  - Course slides, housing, 1996-08 (Box 22)
  - Improving decision-making and patron service in the King County library system, 1996; V-10652 (Box 22)
    Videocassette
- Seires VI. CRP at Cornell
  - Cornell in NYC, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    Two e-mails regarding expanding CRP presence in NYC and a page of notes
  - Web Report, 2003-09-03 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    Memo regarding SMC's efforts to improve the department webstite and Soulellis Studio recommendations for full site architecture
  - CRP Publicity, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    Files on promotion of the department
  - Self-Study, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    Materials relating to self-study of 1999 as well as a copy of 2002 self-study
  - Ph.D. Program Review, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    Material related to department review of Ph.D. program, including a survey of Ph.D. students
  - Faculty Search Advice, Fall 2003 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    A couple of articles and a memo from Ned Rightor on how to conduct a job interview
  - Strategic Direction Committee, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    Memos from SMC and Walter Cohen
  - CRP Admin, Spring 2003 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    A set of documents about the department entittled CRP Administration Documents
  - Community/Economic Dev Degree Programs, Undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    Material related to CRP and other's urban economic development concentrations
  - CRP Curriculum Reform, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Research Plan/AAP, 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    Notes on and preparing for various meetings on researh
  - New Department Initiatives, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Strategic Planning, 1999-07-22 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    Contains examples of strategic planning plans, and a memo from SMC requesting the same, along with asking about sabbatical arrangements with Cambridge University etc.
  - Realignment, 1999-2002 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    Documents relating to the proposed creation of the Cornell School of Governence and Public Affairs as well as the report of the CRP Realignment Committee three years later.
  - Overhead/CHE, Undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    Notes and documentation related to trends in hiring at Cornell
  - Cleveland Projects, 2014-2015 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    Notes about CRP setting up internships and other projects in Cleveland. Includes Kieran Doneghy letter to Joseph Keithley following up on a meeting about possible plans. Also contains student applications for internships
  - 2007 Viewbook, 2007 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    Materials related to remaking the CRP viewbook.
  - Shrinking Cities Gentrification, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    Some materials including correspondence about the possibility of the department putting on a conference about shrinking cities
  - Receipts to submit, 2003-2015 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - SLOAN project, 2006-2007 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - SLOAN, NYS Media proposals, 2006-05 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Website updates, 2007-03-20 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Pre-proposal for Day Hall discussion, Cornell's economic impact on NYS, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Mentoring Committee, 1988-2001 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Thesis workshop materials, Undated (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Internships, Undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
- Series VII. Editorial work
  - Brexit Issue, Undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    Notes for Cambridge Journal of Regions, Economy, Society (CJRES) special issue
  - Regional Studies Editorship, Undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    Materials related to SMC editorship of the Regional Studies book series for Taylor and Francis
  - CJRES Pending, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    Notes related to CJRES issues
  - Policy/RSA Article, 2015 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Invitations for Editorial Boards, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Manufacturing Issue of CJRES, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - The psychology of climate change communication guide, 2010 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Series VIII. Career related
  - Susan Christopherson: Research Orientation and Agenda, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    A five-page summary of her work and work trajectory
  - Center for the Study of the Entertainment Industry, 2002-07-15 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    A proposal draft coauthored by Allen Scott to establish a study center at UCLA, with notes from SMC at the end
  - Meeting Notes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    3 pages of notes from a meeting--ILR folks involved or discussed
  - CVs, 1999-2004 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    CVs and a few notes
  - SC June 04, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Notes for a memo to Ken Reardon regarding her position and the future trajectory of the department
  - Citations of My Work, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Copies of papers that cite SMC, mostly from before 2000
  - Research Orientation and Agenda, Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Document that is likely written for tenure promotion package as it discusses her activities during "the past six years"
  - Promotion Support?, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    A set of SMC articles and an invitation from the Acting Director of the U.S. Department of Labor Women's Bureau, Delores Crockett asking SMC to serve as a US Delegate to a conference in Oslo hosted by the Government of Norway and OECD.
  - Tenure File, Undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    SMC tenure package
  - Third Year Review, 1999-08-11-1999-12-03 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Consideration of improving CRP's approach to 3rd year review
  - Personal History, Undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Collection of articles, etc. w/SMC
  - CRP Executive Committee 2003, 2003-04-14 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Memo to executive committee requesting a conversation regarding comments about her performance in the department.
  - Newspaper Coverage of Grad Student Project, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Report of presentation of Master's project to local state assembleyman, Martin Luster
  - Promotion Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Promotion Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Contains course evaluation results
  - Calendar and stay in Puerto Rico, 2015-08-2016-02 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Abbreviated curriculum vitae, 2015-10 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Urban sustain funding, Atkinson funding, 2015-05 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Trebloc site, Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - RRPC project, 2015-01-28 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Watkins Glen testimony, 2014-10-2015-02 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Seneca wineries project, 2015-01 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Town hall, 2015-03 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Park props, 2015 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Talking points, preliminary proposal, a comprehensive economic impact analysis of natural gas extraction in the Marcellus shale, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Women's planning forum, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Orientation remarks, 2000-2004 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - DGS, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 20)